Guide to the Margaret Flory Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Junior Year Abroad (JYA) Program, Series III
  - Publications
    - "Encounter in Study and Fellowship," M. Flory, in WSCF Federation News (August 1957) (Box 21, Folder 117)
    - JYA "Travel Memos" to students, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 118)
    - JYA "Bibliographies" for students (national, regional, general in scope), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 119)
    - JYA10, ten-year commemorative paper bound volume, J.A. Gittings, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 120)
  - Evaluations
    - JYA Office of Student Work and Student Evaluations of program, 1956-1963 (Box 22, Folder 121-123)
    - JYA Office of Student Work and Student Evaluations of program, 1956-1963 (Box 22, Folder 124)
    - Third-Year "Evaluation of the JYA Program", distillation of evaluations by students and field advisors, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 125)
    - "JYA Ten-Year Evaluation", in-house, two copies w/assoc. materials, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 125a)
    - Tenth Anniversary Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 125b)
    - Evaluation Report, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 125c)
  - JYA Merged Correspondence Files-1952-1965
    - Correspondence, 1952-1965 (Box 23, Folder 126-127f)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1965 (Box 119, Folder 1340)
  - Participating Universities Files
    - Lebanon, American University of Beirut, Beirut College for Women, 1955-1964 (Box 24, Folder 127g-127h)
    - Japan, International Christian University, Tokyo, 1958,1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 128-128a)
    - India, Wilson College, 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 129)
    - India, Isabella Thoburn College, 1957-1964 (Box 25, Folder 130)
    - India, Christian Medical College, Vellore (Women's Christian College), 1953-1963 (Box 25, Folder 131)
    - India, Allahabad University, 1956-1963 (Box 25, Folder 132)
    - Hong Kong, Chung Chi College (Chinese University of Hong Kong), 1960-1965 (Box 25, Folder 133)
    - Guatemala, University of San Carlos, 1951-1953 (Box 25, Folder 134)
    - Ghana, University of, 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 135)
    - Germany, Schiller Coll., Goethe Instit., Tech. Univ., Staatliche Music, 1958-1965 (Box 25, Folder 136)
    - Germany, Berlin, Free University of, 1956-1964 (Box 25, Folder 137)
    - Germany, Miscellaneous, 1958-1964 (Box 25, Folder 138)
    - France, SU, Univ.'s of Grenoble, Neuchatel, Ecole Berlitz, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 139)
    - France, SU, University of Geneva, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 140)
    - Egypt, American University at Cairo, 1956-1960 (Box 26, Folder 141)
    - Chile, University of Concepcion, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 142)
    - Brazil, Univ. of Sao Paolo, Mackenzie Univ., 1959-1961 (Box 26, Folder 143)
    - Sierra Leone, Fourah Bay College (Univ. Col. of Sierra Leone), 1962-1964 (Box 26, Folder 144)
    - Spain, University of Madrid, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 145)
    - Philippines, University of, Silliman University, 1960-1965 (Box 26, Folder 146)
    - Nigeria, Univ. Coll., Ibadan, 1959-1964 (Box 26, Folder 147)
    - Pakistan, Forman Christian College, Lahore, 1952-1960 (Box 26, Folder 147a)
    - Mexico, National University of, 1959-1964 (Box 26, Folder 148)
    - Switzerland, Univ.'s of Geneva, Neuchatel; language study reqmt., 1960-1966 (Box 27, Folder 149)
  - JYA Alumni Regional Retreats
    - Retreats, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 150-151)
  - JYA Tenth Anniversary 1953-1963 Alumni Questionnaires
    - Participant academic years abroad: 1953-1955, 1955-1956, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 152)
    - Participant academic years abroad: 1956-1957 to 1962-1963, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 154-160)
  - JYA Fiftieth Anniversary
    - Short Biographies of JYA Alumni, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 1341)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Alumni Surveys A-B, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 1342)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Alumni Surveys C-G, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 1343)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Alumni Surveys H-K, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 1344)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Alumni Surveys L-N, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 1345)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Alumni Surveys O-R, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 1346)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Alumni Surveys S-W, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 1347)
  - Seminary Year Abroad (NSCF Pilot Project)
    - Establishment of the Program, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 161)
    - Memos, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 162)
    - General Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 163)
    - Hull, Patrick Lewis (Fritz), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 164)
    - Ohlson, Ronald W., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 164a)
- Student Study Seminars, Series IV
  - International/North America
    - Christian Responsibility in the World of Nations Study Seminar, New York City, 1955-1957 (Box 29, Folder 165-165a)
  - Latin America
    - Latin American Affairs Conference (Pittsburgh)
      - Conference, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 165b)
    - Brazil Study Seminar, 1959
      - General (Box 29, Folder 166-167)
      - General (Box 120, Folder 1348)
      - Lectures, Paul Lehmann (Harvard Divinity) (Box 29, Folder 168)
      - Lectures, James McCord (Princeton Theological) (Box 29, Folder 169)
    - Latin American Study Seminar, 1964
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 170-173a)
      - Publications, promotional (Box 30, Folder 174)
      - "Continent in Revolution: Diary-Report of the Latin American Study Seminar, 1964", 1965 (Box 30, Folder 175)
      - Diary Report, Draft Material (Box 30, Folder 175a)
      - Photograph: Guatemala Travel Seminar, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 175a1)
  - Europe
    - Christian-Marxist Dialogue Seminar, 1968
      - Correspondence, etc. (Box 30, Folder 175b-175c)
  - Africa
    - Miscellaneous Conferences and Seminars
      - Kenya in New Concord Conference, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 176)
      - African Affairs Seminar, Washington, DC, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 177)
      - U.N. Seminar on South Africa, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 177a)
      - Africa's Africa Conference (NSCF/WSCF), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 177b)
    - Ghana Study Seminar, Accra, 1961
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 31, Folder 178)
      - Publications( promotional), photographs (Box 31, Folder 179)
      - Seminar instructional materials, including addresses by Ghanaian officials (Box 31, Folder 180)
      - "A Diary-Report, The Ghana Study Seminar" (Box 31, Folder 181)
    - Southern Africa Study Seminar, 1966
      - Publications, promotional and informational (Box 31, Folder 182)
      - General: correspondence, planning memoranda (Box 32, Folder 183-185)
      - Participant Screening Committee Materials (Box 32, Folder 186)
      - Participant Application Materials (Box 32, Folder 187)
      - Seminar Evaluation Materials, including correspondence with participants en route, photographs (Box 32, Folder 188)
    - Afro-Asian Study Seminar, 1963
      - General File, publications, including seminar report: "Looking Toward the New Africa" (Box 33, Folder 189)
    - Middle East Study Seminars, 1960, 1965, 1976
      - Publications, participant evaluations of seminar, correspondence (Box 33, Folder 190)
      - Publications (Box 120, Folder 1349)
      - "Diary Report of the Middle East Study Seminar", 1965 (Box 33, Folder 190a)
      - Participant Evaluations (Box 33, Folder 190b)
  - Asia
    - Asian Student Conference, Berkeley (canceled)
      - General (Box 33, Folder 191)
    - Asia Study Seminars, 1962, 1965, 1967
      - General Files, correspondence, memoranda, 1965, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 192)
      - East Asia S.S., publications(promotional), photographs, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 193-194)
      - "Looking East: Report of the East Asia Study Seminar", 3 copies, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 195)
      - Correspondence files (Box 34, Folder 196-197)
    - Southeast Asia International Study Seminar, 1967
      - General (Box 34, Folder 198)
      - General (Box 120, Folder 1350)
      - Schedules (Box 34, Folder 198a)
      - Budget (Box 34, Folder 198b)
      - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 198c-198g)
- Association of Presbyterian University Pastors (APUP), Series V
  - Correspondence, memoranda, "Reports" from overseas pastors 1954-1966
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1954-1958 (Box 34a, Folder 199-201)
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1960-1963 (Box 35, Folder 202-207)
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 208-210)
  - Overseas Assignment Committee
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1956-1963 (Box 36, Folder 211-213)
    - Correspondence, memos, reports, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 214)
    - (NCMA), 1967 (Box 37, Folder 214a)
  - European Staff Seminars 1961, 1963
    - General, correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 215-218)
    - Correspondence -- Frelick, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 219)
    - General, 1963 Seminar (Box 37, Folder 220)
  - Conferences
    - Conferences, 1951-1963 (Box 37, Folder 221-223)
    - Campus Ministry Convocation, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 224-225)
    - College Chaplains Conference, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 226)
    - Joint Staff Conferences, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 227)
    - New Staff Seminars, 1959-1963 (Box 38, Folder 228)
    - Regional Conferences, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 229)
    - Campus Christian Life, 1959-1960 (Box 38, Folder 230)
  - Miscellaneous
    - General Materials, 1952-1953 (Box 38, Folder 231)
    - Policy Group on WSCF, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 231a)
    - Executive Committee, 1955-1963 (Box 38, Folder 232)
    - Study Papers on Campus Ministry, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 233)
    - Mailings -- Contents Lists, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 233a)
  - National Campus Ministry Association
    - General, 1965-1967 (Box 38, Folder 234)
    - National Conference for Campus Ministers, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 235)
- Ecumenical Student Movement in the United States, Series VI
  - Commission on World Mission (formerly Student Volunteer Movement)
    - General, 1961-1966 (Box 39, Folder 236)
    - Frontier Seminars, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 236a)
    - Nominating Committee, 1960-1965 (Box 39, Folder 237)
    - Nominating Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 238)
    - NSCF Restructure, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 239)
    - 17th Quadrennial, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 240)
    - 17th and 18th Quadrennial -- Programs, 1956, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 1351)
    - 18th Quadrennial, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 241-242)
    - 18th Quadrennial -- Addresses, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 243)
    - 18th Quadrennial -- Planning Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 244)
    - 18th Quadrennial -- Evaluations/Follow-Up, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 245)
    - 18th Quadrennial -- "New Patterns of Obedience in Mission," by M. Flory in Concern, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 245a)
    - 18th Quadrennial -- News Clippings, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 245b)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Administration Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 246)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Advisory Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 247)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Executive Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 248)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Interviews Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 249)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Program Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 250)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Promotion/Preparation, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 251)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Publications, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 252)
    - 19th Quadrennial -- Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 253)
    - 20th Quadrennial -- Planning Committee (cf. UCM Process '67), 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 254)
  - National Student Christian Federation (1959-1966)
    - Committees
      - Budget and Finance Committee, 1959-1966 (Box 40, Folder 255-257)
      - Central Committee, 1962-1966 (Box 40, Folder 258-260)
      - Committee on Christian Work Among International Students, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 261)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on the Dominican Republic, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 262)
      - Committee on Ecumenical Voluntary Service, 1959-1966 (Box 41, Folder 263)
      - Latin American Concerns Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 264-266)
      - Personnel Committee, 1961-1966 (Box 41, Folder 267)
      - Committee of Program and Study Secretaries, 1961-1966 (Box 41, Folder 268-269)
      - Committee on Southern Africa, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 269a)
    - General
      - General, 1959-1966 (Box 41, Folder 270)
      - Constitution and By-laws, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 270a)
      - "An Ecumenical Strategy for the National Student Christian Federation," Leonard Clough, Seventh General Assembly, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 270b)
      - Restructure, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 271-272)
  - University Christian Movement (1966-1969)
    - Annual Assemblies
      - 1st Annual Assembly (NSCF 8th General Assembly), 1966 (Box 42, Folder 273)
      - 1st Annual Assembly -- Minutes, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 274)
      - 1st Annual Assembly -- Articles of Operation, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 275)
      - 2nd Annual Assembly, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 276)
      - 3rd Annual Assembly, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 277)
    - Committees and Councils
      - Advisory Council, 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 278)
      - Budget and Finance Committee, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 279)
      - General Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 280-281)
      - Committee on International Ecumenical Ministries, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 282)
      - Correspondence and Reports: International Student Movements, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 282a)
      - Latin American Concerns Committee, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 283)
      - Latin American Task Force, Mexico Orientation, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 283a)
      - Personnel Committee, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 284)
      - Southern Africa Committee, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 285)
      - Turku Committee, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 286)
    - Programs, Events, and Miscellaneous
      - Consultations on the University and World Change, 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 287)
      - Consultation on University and World Change #2: Inter-American Focus (Austin, Tex.), 1966 (Box 43, Folder 287a)
      - Proposed Puerto Rico Project, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 288)
      - Staff Conference, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 289)
      - Memo regarding Heiko Rohrbach, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 289a)
      - Education and Social Change: Notes from the UCM Files, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 1352)
      - U.S. History Symposium, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 290)
      - WSCF Conference, Turku, Finland -- Correspondence re: travel, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 291)
      - Steve Johnson Paper, "What are we going to do with our lives?", 1968 (Box 43, Folder 292)
      - Dissolution of the UCM, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 293)
      - Dissolution of the UCM, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 1352)
    - Cleveland Week of Process '67 (20th Quadrennial)
      - General (Box 43, Folder 294-295)
      - Roster (Box 43, Folder 296)
      - Education Through Dialogue (Box 43, Folder 297)
      - Internationalization (Box 43, Folder 298-299)
  - United Student Christian Council
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 300)
    - WSCF World Teaching Conference, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 301)
  - United Campus Christian Fellowship (1960-1968)
    - Establishment, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 302)
    - Minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 44, Folder 303)
    - Campus Movements -- Howard U., 1963 (Box 44, Folder 304)
    - Campus Movements -- Bowling Green State U., Michigan State, 1964, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 305)
    - National Conference, East Lansing, Michigan, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 306-307)
    - National Consultation: "The Aim of Higher Education," St. Louis U., 1966 (Box 44, Folder 308-309)
  - United Ministries in Higher Education
    - General, 1965-1968 (Box 44, Folder 310)
    - Report: Teaching Religion in Tax Supported Colleges and Universities, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 310a)
    - Letter/Report on Asia by M. Flory, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 311)
    - National Staff, 1966 Jan-Jun (Box 44, Folder 312)
    - National Staff, 1966 Jul-1969 (Box 45, Folder 313-316)
    - Council for Policy and Strategy, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 317)
    - Committee on International Concerns, 1966-1968 (Box 45, Folder 318-319)
    - Internationalization, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 320-323a)
    - University Ministries and United States/Latin American Policy Study (Danforth Foundation), 1975 (Box 45, Folder 323a1)
  - Regional/Denominational Groups (WSCF Associated Organizations)
    - California Student Christian Movement, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 323b)
    - New York Student Christian Movement, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 1353)
    - UCM in New England, Directory, 1978-1980 (Box 120, Folder 1354)
    - UCM in New England, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 323c)
  - Ecumenical Student Movement after the UCM
    - "The Student Christian Movement in Perspective," Seminar, Blue Ridge Assembly, North Carolina, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 323)
    - National Ecumenical Student Conference I, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 324)
    - National Ecumenical Student Conference, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 1356)
    - National Interim Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 46, Folder 325)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 1355)
    - National Ecumenical Student Conference II, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 326)
    - National Ecumenical Student Christian Council, 1983-1986 (Box 46, Folder 327)
    - National Ecumenical Student Conference Brochures and Newsletters, 1984, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 1357)
    - National Ecumenical Student Conferences, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 328)
    - Council for Ecumenical Student Christian Ministry, 1986-2002 (Box 46, Folder 329-331a)
    - Minutes, Staff Reports, and Working Papers, 1987-1989 (Box 120, Folder 1358)
    - Memo re: The Big Event, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 1359)
    - National Association of College and University Chaplains, Directory, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 331b)
    - CESCM National Gatherings, 1990, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 332)
    - SCM -- Ecumenical Student Movement after the UCM. Miscellaneous/Printed material., n.d. (Box 46, Folder 332a)
    - Franklin J. Woo, "A Goodly Heritage of a Century of Student Christian Movement", 1991 (Box 46, Folder 332b)
- World's Student Christian Federation, Series VII
  - Regional Offices
    - Interregional Office
      - General, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 333)
    - Africa
      - General, 1957-1981 (Box 47, Folder 334-335)
      - African Student Seminar, 1961-1965 (Box 47, Folder 336)
      - All Africa Student Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 337)
      - West Africa Leadership Training Course, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 338)
      - UCM of Southern Africa, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 1247)
    - Asia-Pacific
      - General, 1964-1995 (Box 47, Folder 339-340)
      - General, 1996-2004 (Box 111, Folder 1248)
      - Rangoon Conference: Tambaram, India, 1958 (Box 111, Folder 1249)
      - Preparation for Rangoon Conference: Tambaram, India, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 1360)
      - National SCMs: India, Indonesia, Korea, Singapore, 1966-1973 (Box 47, Folder 341)
      - Asian International Study Fellowship, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 342)
      - Asian University Teachers Conference, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 342a)
      - Leadership Training Program, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 342b)
    - Europe
      - General, 1968-1990 (Box 111, Folder 1250)
      - Publications, 1970-2001 (Box 111, Folder 1251)
    - Latin America
      - General, 1959-1986 (Box 48, Folder 344-345)
      - Sao Paulo Conference, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 346)
      - Latin American Department Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 346a)
    - Middle East
      - General, 1968-1981 (Box 48, Folder 347)
      - General, 1982-2004 (Box 111)
      - Middle East Project, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 348)
    - North America
      - General, 1974-1987 (Box 48, Folder 349)
      - Toronto Meeting, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 350)
      - Student Christian Movement of Canada, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 350a)
  - Trustees and Finance
    - General, 1953-1971 (Box 114, Folder 1293)
    - Trustees, 1972-1986 (Box 114, Folder 1294-1298)
    - Trustees, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 1361)
    - North American Partners Consultation, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 1299)
    - Trustees, 1987-1997 (Box 114, Folder 1300-1303)
    - Senior Friends, 1974-1995 (Box 115, Folder 1304-1305)
    - Committee on Friends of WSCF -- General (Box 115, Folder 1306)
    - Finance, 1973-1979 (Box 115, Folder 1307-1308)
    - Senior Friends Gifts, 1982-1983 (Box 115, Folder 1309)
    - Finance, 1980-1983 (Box 116, Folder 1310)
    - Senior Friends, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 1311)
    - Finance, 1985-1995 (Box 116, Folder 1312-1316)
  - Committees and Commissions
    - Commission on Foreign Students
      - Minutes, 1960-1967 (Box 48, Folder 351)
      - General, 1960-1963 (Box 48, Folder 352-353)
      - Consultation: "A New Ministry in a New World," Bossey, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 354)
      - Consultation, Bossey, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 355-356)
      - Christian Care for African Students in East Germany, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 356a)
      - General, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 357)
      - Minutes, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 358-359)
      - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 360)
      - General, 1966-1967 (Box 49, Folder 361-364)
      - Korean Students' Conference, Pittsburgh, Nov. 23-26, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 364a)
      - Joint North American/European Committee, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 365)
      - General, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 366)
      - Graduate School of Ecumenical Studies, Bossey: List of Students, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 366a)
      - "Brain Drain", 1965-1969 (Box 50, Folder 367)
      - Asian Christian Student Conference in Europe, 1961-1964 (Box 50, Folder 368)
    - New Headquarters Committee (Philippe Maury Memorial)
      - General, correspondence, 1965-1980 (Box 50, Folder 369-372)
    - Miscellaneous Committees
      - Ad Hoc Screening Committee, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 373)
      - Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 374)
      - Advisory Committee: Mission Board Relationships, 1965-1969 (Box 50, Folder 375-376)
      - Church Relationship Committee, 1977-1983 (Box 50, Folder 377)
      - Development Task Force, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 378)
      - Executive Committee -- Notes, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 379)
      - Executive Committee -- Reports, Correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box 51, Folder 380)
      - General Committee, Nasrapur, India -- Correspondence and Recording, 1953 (Box 111, Folder 1253)
      - General Committee -- U.S. Delegation, 1960, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 381-382)
  - Assemblies, Conferences, Meetings and Seminars
    - General Assemblies
      - WSCF - Conference: Tambaram, 1952 (Box 111, Folder 1254)
      - 24th General Assembly, Embalse Rio Tercero, Argentina, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 1255)
      - 26th General Assembly, Addis Ababa, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 382a)
      - 26th General Assembly, Addis Ababa, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 1362)
      - 27th General Assembly, Colombo, Notes, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 383)
      - 28th General Assembly, San Francisco, Host Committee, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 384)
      - 30th General Assembly, Chantilly, France, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 385)
      - 31st General Assembly, Yamoussoukro, Cote d'Ivoire, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 386)
    - Miscellaneous Meetings and Conferences
      - Asian Student Christian Seminar, Geneva, "Towards Full Participation in Nation Building", 1966 (Box 111, Folder 1256)
      - Consultation on Ecumenical Strategy in the Universities of Asia, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 1364)
      - Education for Liberation Workshop, Rome, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 1257)
      - Executive Meeting Report: Montreal, Canada, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 1258)
      - Executive Committee Annual Report, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 1259)
      - Executive Committee: General, 1977-2004 (Box 111, Folder 1260)
      - General Committee, Frankfurt Kirchentag, Germany, 1956 (Box 121, Folder 1365)
      - Leadership Training Conference, Mexico City, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 387)
      - Meeting Schedule, 1989 (Box 121, Folder 1363)
      - Middle Generation Conference, Toronto, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 388)
      - Mission Board Involvement in Overseas University Work Consultation, Tuxedo Park, NY, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 1261)
      - Monmouth Conference, 1958 (Box 111, Folder 1262)
      - Consultation on Missionary Strategy, Monmouth, Ill., 1954 (Box 52, Folder 389)
      - Consultation of Movement Research Groups, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 390)